[
    {
        "question": "get to kamakura",
        "category": "how",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1ISTe8KQB4v-Wm19TT-xJc1puycew-s5MJEtNe2lMkR4/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "buy narita express ticket",
        "category": "how",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/16zzxKBCK1m56R0bcc2pX4_Wy7fLzbA5hAUw1mVJpOxg/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "take trains to mt.fuji",
        "category": "where",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1RQX6wkPqbIqNyetOy9CJ8n92hdM0IjtrTtB_-aW5P_E/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "pick up tickets",
        "category": "where",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1pa4nyPDlq5zs66PAdws9bfLGu7HnWM3CE7aGSxnVfvE/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "is 3d cat",
        "category": "where",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/10iOoOb6UJfgyrnPrS-HSOcFSgrxpdXtkdK61dY7WSAQ/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "is romance car",
        "category": "where",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1IYxmQkrZaTy4uaSG67S_VcYyW4rfggSahKlEwA8A-rw/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "buy subway tickets",
        "category": "where",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1zEolnUDgP4uh_gBaZbo6-Dx7kiEZcsJScKPRWxmhrqQ/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "go to ginza",
        "category": "how",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1zEolnUDgP4uh_gBaZbo6-Dx7kiEZcsJScKPRWxmhrqQ/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "buy tickets to hakone",
        "category": "how",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1IYxmQkrZaTy4uaSG67S_VcYyW4rfggSahKlEwA8A-rw/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "book narita express by my ticket",
        "category": "how",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/16zzxKBCK1m56R0bcc2pX4_Wy7fLzbA5hAUw1mVJpOxg/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "buy tickets to osaka",
        "category": "how",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/17eYiErPNbcbTu67T7h8FQX2u7XLobbvcPaI_T6sZuMs/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "buy nex tickets",
        "category": "where",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/16zzxKBCK1m56R0bcc2pX4_Wy7fLzbA5hAUw1mVJpOxg/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "go to get to mt.fuji",
        "category": "where",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1RQX6wkPqbIqNyetOy9CJ8n92hdM0IjtrTtB_-aW5P_E/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "buy suica card",
        "category": "where",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1kNGkQGHNo7G8sRkQS0DcYoUHhR1CN-KFM3_V5gUxriQ/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "buy tickets to kyoto",
        "category": "how",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/17eYiErPNbcbTu67T7h8FQX2u7XLobbvcPaI_T6sZuMs/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "buy suica for child",
        "category": "where",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1kNGkQGHNo7G8sRkQS0DcYoUHhR1CN-KFM3_V5gUxriQ/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "is toilet",
        "category": "where",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/10iOoOb6UJfgyrnPrS-HSOcFSgrxpdXtkdK61dY7WSAQ/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "is keio line",
        "category": "where",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1WSOcEfsOAE-CCNKmbX12Y49if9YSkr4lIcmCp8faqQg/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "is odakyu line",
        "category": "where",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1IYxmQkrZaTy4uaSG67S_VcYyW4rfggSahKlEwA8A-rw/edit?usp=sharing"
    },
    {
        "question": "is odakyu sightseeing center",
        "category": "where",
        "answer": "https://docs.google.com/document/d/1IYxmQkrZaTy4uaSG67S_VcYyW4rfggSahKlEwA8A-rw/edit?usp=sharing"
    }
]